

About Me

Frontend Developer with over 6 months of market experience in React.js, gained through the internships, delivering user-friendly and responsive web applications.

Contact

- +92 3180029219
- wasaysaleem071@gmail.com
- H.no 213 Usmania colony Nazimabad No 1 Karachi

స్ట్లో Skills

- HTML / CSS
- Tailwind css
- Javascript / Typescript
- React.js / Next.js
- Redux Toolkit

At Language

- English
- Urdu

Abdul Wasay

FrontEnd Web Developer



Links

- MY PORTFOLIO
- GITHUB PROJECTS
- LINKED IN PROFILE

Education

(2021 - present)

UNIVERSITY OF KARACHI (UBIT)

Undergraduate in Computer Science 3.35

(2019 - 2021)

GOVT DEHLI COLLEGE

Intermediate in Pre-Engineering A+

Experience

(Mar 2024 - July 2024)

JUNIOR REACT.JS DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP)

mParsec

- contributed to a large-scale realworld product of the company.
- Developed optimize features in React

(Jan 2024 - Mar 2024)
FRONTEND DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP)

Web3gle

- Developed a major Booking system web application on React.js
- Optimize the performance of Web app